O
His marketing.
OK
Pulang.
Good morning ok the name is.
Oh okay,
everything is fine,
everything is fine.
This is pharmacy delivery.
Yes,
that's what you asked,
it doesn't say anxiety and stress medicine here.
No no don't let me see what the name is.
There are four shots you can take every three hours.
Alive. A
people don't charge any medicine just the delivery fee.
My name fell.
Staying with him just because of his care is just your initiative.
Thanks old guy I'm going to buy it for this.
Believe me,
I'm a very smart medicine you need.
I just thank you so much.
It saw?
Have a great day.
Sent on Mars bro caraca congratulations I'm just staying because of Mars.
Because it was wild now you sent me to think about it?
Okay hand?
Every three hours
delivery fee only.
Thank you Xuxa dammit bro who maxed out old man was very apprehensive
that he wasn't going to give some happiness gratitude bro.
I thank you.